<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>本来无一物</title>
    <link>https://ginhton.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 本来无一物</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 19:56:36 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ginhton.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Paper Question</title>
      <link>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/paper-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 19:56:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/paper-questions/</guid>
      <description>questions for papers It is embarassing being asked to ask questions about papers that you don&amp;rsquo;t understand. So here are some templates for you.
data  can we get that data? open source? is it proper to use that data? outdated, special? how do they get their data? how do they process their data?  method  what is its core method? what are the corresponding method in other paper? can we implement that method?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sink</title>
      <link>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/stuff15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 20:55:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/stuff15/</guid>
      <description>list  read novel successfully defeat bad idea  feel  from zhihu: if you have something that you are really interested in, you will not always want to play games or do something bad. So the method can save me from games and meaninglessness is to find my interest and do it. I admit I cannot focus on my paper. Nothind else. jiayou  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>shige</title>
      <link>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/stuff14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 20:51:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/stuff14/</guid>
      <description>list  read novels sleep too much watch a video about taizaizhi  feel  I remeber that an old friend told me things about taizaizhi in days before. At that time, I did not know taizaizhi, even this name. But I said something bad about him and end our talk unhappily. Now I know I donnot know. I appologise. life is a marathon. jia you.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuff13</title>
      <link>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/stuff13/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 00:39:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/stuff13/</guid>
      <description>list  read novel all day cut hair for my father resist bad idea once succesfully  feel  this is for yesterday. sleep well recently  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pause</title>
      <link>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/stuff12/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 21:50:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/stuff12/</guid>
      <description>simple  novel sleep  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>patience</title>
      <link>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/stuff11/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 21:19:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/stuff11/</guid>
      <description>list  download some books read half chapter lisp exercise typing anki 5 minutes write blog read introduction and related work of one paper  feel  the most exciting thing is that I unlock s key in keybr.com today, spend more time relaxing. Read novels, like longzu and zhetian. Finding new books to read. The most proud thing is that I did meditation for 300-breath last mid-night. talk a lot with my sister.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a title</title>
      <link>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/stuff7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 19:23:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/stuff7/</guid>
      <description>list  listen to many podcasts sleep for the whole afternoon (maybe last night it was code and I did&amp;rsquo;t sleep well) find a browser add-on to hide scroll bar  feeling  now, it&amp;rsquo;s 07:24 PM. I read the introduction of a paper. I think I can read one more chapter about lisp. At 08:42 PM, I finished reading lisp. I am so good! I will rest for some time, and later write down the example code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a title</title>
      <link>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/stuff6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 23:06:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/stuff6/</guid>
      <description>list  find podcast app and some podcast listen to some podcast read one paper that downloaded last night read one chaper about lisp programming download some videos about xiamu  special feel   I am tired after dinner. So giving up continuing my reading, find podcast instead. A way for relax, at least, relax for eyes. After one hour or more, I still feel tired and lack of intention to study.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>three thousand</title>
      <link>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/stuff5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 19:36:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/stuff5/</guid>
      <description>hugo command  hugo generate blog hugo server boot a live-reload server in localhost hugo new posts/hi.md generete hi.md in posts directory  personal life  read one chapter blog about common lisp. try to give up gaming (Well, again. Though I failed a lot of times) read a chapter of ZhiLe downloads a bunch of songs. listen and listen. Well, stop taking note. I want to write down the things about myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuff4</title>
      <link>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/stuff4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 21:59:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/stuff4/</guid>
      <description>lisp eq eql equal   eq use to compare address of the items. If they are in the same address, then they are eq. eq is used to compare symbol, not string, not number, not list.
  eql is more general than eq. (eql &#39;foo &#39;foo) =&amp;gt; t, (eql 3 3) =&amp;gt; t, (eql 3 3.0) =&amp;gt; nil, different types.. eql compares the addresses of two object. if the two are of the same type, eql compares their value.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>