<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>本来无一物</title>
    <link>https://ginhton.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 本来无一物</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 19:23:45 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ginhton.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>a title</title>
      <link>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/stuff7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 19:23:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/stuff7/</guid>
      <description>list  listen to many podcasts sleep for the whole afternoon (maybe last night it was code and I did&amp;rsquo;t sleep well) find a browser add-on to hide scroll bar  feeling  now, it&amp;rsquo;s 07:24 PM. I read the introduction of a paper. I think I can read one more chapter about lisp. At 08:42 PM, I finished reading lisp. I am so good! I will rest for some time, and later write down the example code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a title</title>
      <link>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/stuff6/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 23:06:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/stuff6/</guid>
      <description>list  find podcast app and some podcast listen to some podcast read one paper that downloaded last night read one chaper about lisp programming download some videos about xiamu  special feel   I am tired after dinner. So giving up continuing my reading, find podcast instead. A way for relax, at least, relax for eyes. After one hour or more, I still feel tired and lack of intention to study.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>three thousand</title>
      <link>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/stuff5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 19:36:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/stuff5/</guid>
      <description>hugo command  hugo generate blog hugo server boot a live-reload server in localhost hugo new posts/hi.md generete hi.md in posts directory  personal life  read one chapter blog about common lisp. try to give up gaming (Well, again. Though I failed a lot of times) read a chapter of ZhiLe downloads a bunch of songs. listen and listen. Well, stop taking note. I want to write down the things about myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stuff4</title>
      <link>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/stuff4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 21:59:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ginhton.github.io/posts/stuff4/</guid>
      <description>lisp eq eql equal   eq use to compare address of the items. If they are in the same address, then they are eq. eq is used to compare symbol, not string, not number, not list.
  eql is more general than eq. (eql &#39;foo &#39;foo) =&amp;gt; t, (eql 3 3) =&amp;gt; t, (eql 3 3.0) =&amp;gt; nil, different types.. eql compares the addresses of two object. if the two are of the same type, eql compares their value.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>